NLRB Briefs, Petitions and other Legal Documents 5318
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NLRB Briefs, Petitions and other Legal Documents
1935-1958
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States. National War Labor Board (1942-1945)
5318
12 cubic feet
12 linear ft.
Records (documents), briefs (legal documents).
The collection consists of a sample of the briefs, petitions, and other legal documents issued by the National Labor Relations Board in cases which were appealed in the Supreme Court and the various district courts for the period 1937-1951.
5596223
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 05, 2011
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4057 AV: James A. Gross NLRB Audiocassettes /4057 P: James A. Gross NLRB Photographs /4124: James A. Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files /4232: James A. Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files 5240: NLRB Case Files 5355: NLRB vs. International Union of Operating Engineers Local 450 Court Documents 5435 OH: NLRB Oral History Project Miscellaneous 5609: Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 5740 OH: NLRB 50th Anniversary Conference Tapes and Transcripts 5843: NLRB Miscellaneous Tapes and Transcripts 5843 OHM: NLRB Oral History Project II Master Tapes 5843 OHT: NLRB Oral History Project II Transcripts 5906: NLRB Additional Case Files relating to Health Care 6008: Lechmere vs. NLRB Company Legal Files 6021: Theodore W. Kheel Records 6122m: NLRB "Hebrew Free Burial Association, Case AO-279" Papers 6171: NLRB Decisions by Stipulation: Classified Index of National Labor Relations Board Decisions and Related Court Decisions (DS Reports) 6266: NLRB Documents Relating to UAW Alleged Unfair Labor Practices at Caterpillar, Inc.
United States. National Labor Relations Board
5596223
- Acme-Evans, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes "Reply Brief" and "Brief"
- Adelard Lincourt (Box 1, Folder 2)
  No date present on document.
- Adams Motors, Inc., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- J.S. Abercrombie, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Aerovox Corporation, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Agwilines, Inc., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ACME Breweries, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bersted Manufacturing Co., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ACME Mattress Company, Textile Workers of America, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Aintree Corporation, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bethlehem Steel Company, Bethlehem Steel Corporation, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bethlehem Steel Company, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Big Lake Oil Company, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Biles Coleman Lumber Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bill Daniels, Inc. & Walker Motors, Inc., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Prosper Brozen, Individually and doing business as B.B. Crystal Company, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Bryan Manufacturing Corporation, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Buckeye Coal Corporation (Box 1, Folder 18)
  No date on document.
- Building and Construction Trades Council of Pittsburgh, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Burke Machine Tool Company, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Burnette Castings Company, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Burk Brothers, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- T.H. Burns and R.S. Gillespie, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Burry Biscuit Corporation, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Bussmann Employees Association, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Bussmann Manufacturing Company and McGraw Electric Company, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Buzza-Cardozo, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- B&Z Hosiery Products Co., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Boeing Airplane Co., and William M. Allen, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Bogue Electric Company, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Boldemann Chocolate Company, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Bonita Fruit Company (Box 1, Folder 32)
  No date on this document.
- Bonita F (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Bonwit Teller, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- J.A. Booker, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Arthur A. Borchert (West Fork Cut Glass Company), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Marathon Electric Manufacturing, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Aladdin Industries, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Albert Armato, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Albert Leonard, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Algoma Net Company (Box 1, Folder 40)
  This document has no date.
- Hazer & Jaeger Funeral Home, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- J.H. Allison Co., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Alside, Inc., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Alton Miller, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Aluminum Company of America, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Aluminum Goods Manufacturing Company, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Aluminum Ore Company (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Dixie Motor Coach Corporation, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters of America, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- American Broach and Machine Corporation, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- American Car and Foundry Company, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- American Creosoting Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- American District Telegraph Company of Pennsylvania, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- American Erika Corporation, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- American Federation of Grain Millers, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Bailey Company (East Side Branch), 1949 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Baltimore Transit Company, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Bank of America, National Trusts and Savings Association, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- John H. Barr Marketing Co., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Bear Brand Hosiery Co., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Beatrice Foods Company, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Bemis Bro. Bag Co., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- J.A. Bentley Lumber Company, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Berkey & Gay Furniture Company, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Bersted Manufacturing Co., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Bethlehem Shipbuilding Co, Bethlehem Steel Co., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- American Laundry Machinery Co., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Amer Furnace Co., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- American National Bank of St. Paul, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- American National Insurance Company, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- American Newspapers Publishers Association, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- American Pearl Button Co., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- American Potash & Chemical Co., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- American Rolling Mill Company, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- American Refining and Smelting Company, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- American Steel Foundries, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- American Thread Company, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- American White Cross Laboratories, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Pacific Moulded Products Company, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Anchor Rome Mills, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Andrew Jergens Company, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Andre Mackay, Soren P. Thorsen, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Angwell Curtain Company, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- E. Anthony & Sons, Inc., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Appalachian Electric Power Company, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Arcade-Sunshine Company, Inc., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Arlington-Fairfax Broadcasting Co., Inc., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Armour and Company, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Arnolt Motor Company and S.H. Arnolt, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  doing business as Atlas Steel & Tube Company
- The Ann Arbor Press, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Arthur Winer, Inc., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Arthur G. McKee & Company, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Arton Studios, Inc., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Athens Manufacturing Company, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- E.C. Atkins & Company, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Atlanta Metallic Casket Company, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Atlas Life Insurance Company, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Atlanta Brick & Tile Company, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Atlantic Towing Company, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Atlantic Towing Company, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- The Austin Company, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Autopart Manufacturing Company, Universal Parts, Inc., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- American Radio Association, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- The Boss Manufacturing Co., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- J.G. Boswell Company and Corcoran Telephone, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Bradley Lumber Company of Arkansas, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- J.L. Brandeis, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Bretz Fuel Company, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Samuel S. Brody (doing business as Standard Service Bureau), 1951 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Birdsall-Stockdale Motor Company, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Birmingham Post Company, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Black-Clawson Company, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Blair Quarries, Inc., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- D.G. Bland Lumber Company (Box 2, Folder 29)
  (No date available for this document)
- The Blanton Company, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Blue Ridge Shirt Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1949 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  with Fayetteville and Lincoln County Chamber of Commerce
- O.D. Wilson Company, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- American Communications Association, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Charles H. Parsons (d/b/a United Telephones Organization), 1950 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- A.J. Lindemann and Hoverson Company, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- E.C. Brown Company, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Brown Paper Mill Company, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Ozark Dam Constructors, Flippin Materials Co., 1952 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Brown Company, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Brown & Sharpe Manufacturing Co., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Bird Machine Co., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Clinton Cotton Mills, a corporation, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Clipped Instrument Laboratory, Inc., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Clover Fork Coal Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Coal Creek Coal Company, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- S.S. Coachman & Sons Inc., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Coca-Cola Bottling Co. of St. Louis, a corporation, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Colgate-Palmolive-Peet, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Collins & Aikman Corporation, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Collins Baking Company, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Colonie Fibre Company, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Colorado Fuel and Iron Corporation, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Columbian Carbon Company, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Columbian Enameling & Stamping Company, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Combustion Engineering Co., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Comfort Spring Corporation, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Commonwealth Edison Company, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Concordia Ice Company (Box 2, Folder 58)
  (No date was found for this document.)
- Connecticut Chemical Research Corporation, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Conover Motor Company, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Consolidated Machine Tool Corporation, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Consumers Cooperative Refinery Association, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Consumers Power Company, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Consumers Power Company, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Continental Box Company, Inc., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Continental Oil Company, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  Two Cases: NO. 3879, NO. 3356)
- Continental Pipeline Company, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- J.B. Cook Auto Machine Company, Inc., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Corsicana Cotton Mills, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Cowell Portland Cement Company, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Crompton-Highland Mills, Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- J.I. Case Company, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Cedartown Yarn Mills, Inc., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Century Cement Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Charles Albrecht, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Charles Fay (d/b/a Amalgamated Machine Instrument), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Charles C. Hobart, d/b/a Hobard Cabinet Company, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- The Dixie Terminal Company, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Dolores, Inc., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Don Juan, Inc. and Don Juan Co, Inc., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Don Juan, Inc. and Don Juan Co., Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Donnelly Garment Company, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Dorsey Trailers, Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Department Store Employees Union (Box 3, Folder 16)
  No date available.
- Douglas Silk Products Company, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- The Crosby Company (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Dow Chemical Company, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Duncan Foundry and Machine Works, Inc., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- E.I. du Pont de Nemours & Company, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Denver Building and Construction Trades Council (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Several cases. NO. 333, 4171, 3812, 4260, 10271
- De Mornay-Budd, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Detroit Gasket and Manufacturing Company, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Dependable Wholesale Company, Inc., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Diamond Hosiery Corporation, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Dixie Motor Coach Corporation & Sunshine Bus Lines, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Dixie Shirt Company, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Dixie Furniture Company, Inc., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Gonzalez Padin Company, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- George Noroian d/b/a Noroian Company, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Sexton Welding Company, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- George A. Vare, Edwin H. Vare, d/b/a McCarron Co., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- George D. Auchter Company, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- George H. Clark & Mildred H. Clark (d/b/a Clark Phonograph Record Co.), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Charles Bank Stout (Box 3, Folder 36)
  No date available. NO. 10584
- George P. Pilling & Son, Co. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  No date present. NO. 7524
- George W. Reed and International Hod Carriers, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Geraldine Novelty Company, Inc., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Germain Seed and Plant Company, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Gibson County Electric Membership Corporation, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Gilbert Motor Sales, Inc., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Gilfillan Bros, Inc., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Gilson Brothers, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Gittlin Bag Company (d/b/a Gittlin Charlotte Bag Company) (Box 3, Folder 45)
  No date. NO. 6391
- Globe Cotton Mills, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Globe Automatic Sprinkler Company of Pennsylvania, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Global Wireless, Ltd., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Glen Raven Silk Mills, Inc., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Gullet Gin Company, Inc., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Gutmann & Company, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Goodyear Footwear Corporation, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Goodyear Tire & Rubber Company of Alabama, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- The Grace Company, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- W.W. Cross & Company, Inc., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Atlas Coil Spring Company, Kelty Machine Works, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- De Mornay-Budd, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 57)
  SEE FOLDER 23.
- Diamond T Motor Car Company, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Differential Steel Car Company, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- DiGiorgio Fruit Corporation, DiGiorgio Wine Company, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Dixie Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- R.R. Donnelley Sons & Company, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- The Daily Review Corporation, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Dannen Grain and Milling Corporation (Box 3, Folder 64)
  No date available. 12113
- D.W. Owan & Sons, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Davis Motors, Inc., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Dayton Iron & Coal Corp., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Dealers Engine Rebuilders, Inc., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Deena Artware, Inc., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Deena Products Company, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Del E. Webb Construction Company and International Union of Operating Engineers, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  Three cases. NO. 14491, 14,428, and 14,466)
- Chicago Apparatus Company, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Chicago Steel Foundry, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Childs Company and Chain Service Restaurant Employee Union, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Christian Board of Publication, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Cincinnati Chemical Works, Inc., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- The Citizens-News Company, A Corporation, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Clark Bros Co., Inc, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Clayton & Lambart Manufacturing Company, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Clearwater Finishing Company, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- The Cleveland Electric Illuminating Company, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Cleveland Trust Company, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Climax Spinning Company, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Crowley's Milk Company, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Crown Can Company, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Cudahy Packing Company, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Cullen-Thompson Motor Company, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- American Shuffleboard Corporation, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Calcasieu Paper Co., Inc. and Southern Industries Company (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Caldwell Furniture Company, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 8b)
- Reno Employers Council, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Cambria Clay Products, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- S.H. Camp and Company (Box 4, Folder 11)
  No date. NO. 9672
- Cannon Electric Development Company, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- J.R. Cantrall Company, H.C. Smith Company, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Capital Service, Inc., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Carthage Fabrics Corporation, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Claude C. Carnes, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Carolina Mills, Inc., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Caroline Mills, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Documents range from 1946 to 1948.
- Carter Carburetor Company, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- J.I. Case Company, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Stafford Operating Company, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Chattanooga Bakery Inc., Mountain City Mill Company, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Chautua Hardware Corporation (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Two cases: 1951 and 1953
- Cheney California Lumber Company, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Cherry Cotton Mills, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Federal Engineering Company, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Field Packing Company, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Fisher Governor Company, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Fitzpatrick and Weller, Inc., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Foreman's Association of America, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Edward G. Budd Manufacturing Company (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Three cases. Years range from 1946 to 1948
- Edward Brothers Inc., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- El Paso Electric Company, a Corporation, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Flotill Products Inc., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Floyd Drumming (d/b/a Drummond Implement Company), 1953 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Ford Motor Company, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Three cases in the folder.
- Forest-Lawn Memorial Park Association Inc., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Deluxe Motor Stages, Plymouth Coach Division, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Fr (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Frank A. Houriban of Chicago, IL (Box 4, Folder 39)
  No date. This document is an Appeal.
- Franklin Hosiery Mills, Inc., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Frank Bros. Company, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Nelson Industries, Nelson Stamping & Manufacturing Company, Electro-Cap Mold Company, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Fred P. Weissman Company, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- The S. Frieder and Sons Company, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Fuchs Baking Company, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Fairmont Creamery Company, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  Three cases: 2861, 2862, 3610
- Fairfield Engineering Company, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- The Falk Corporation, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Fansteel Metallurgical Corporation, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Farmers' Cooperative Company, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Farmers' Electric Co-operative, Inc., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Fast Trucking, Inc., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Faultless Caster Corporation, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- General Armature and Manufacturing Co., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- General Shoe Corporation (Box 4, Folder 56)
  Two Cases: 11832 (dated 1953) and 11381 (dated 1951)
- General Motors Corporation (Box 4, Folder 57)
  Two Cases: 8814 (dated 1945), [no case number[ (dated 1949)
- W.C. and Agues Graham (d/b/a Graham Ship Repair), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- W.T. Grant Co., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Great Southern Tracking Company, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Greater New York Broadcasting Corporation, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Grede Foundries Inc., Iron Mountain Division, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- J. Greenebaum Tanning Company, a Corporation, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Coca-Cola Bottling Company, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- The Greenport Basin & Construction Company, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Greenville Cotton Oil Company, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Greenville Steel Car Company, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Grieder Machine Tool & Die Company, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Grower Shipper Vegetable Association of Central California, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Gulf Public Service Company, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Gagnon Plating and Manufacturing Company, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Gamble-Robinson Company (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Gate City Cotton Mills, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Gatke Corporation, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- S.W. Evans & Son, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Eva-Ray Dress Manufacturing Company, Inc. and Petite Tot, Inc., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Ever Ready Label Corporation, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- E.A. Laboratories, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Earl B. Law and Donald T. Law, d/b/a E.B. Law and Son, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Eagle Manufacturing Company, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 80)
- Eagle-Picher Mining and Smelting Company, a Corporation, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 81)
- Earl I. Sifers d/b/a Sifers Candy Company (Box 4, Folder 82)
  This document has no date. NO. 3671
- East Texas Steel Castings Company, Inc., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 83)
- Eastern Coal Corporation, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 84)
- Eastern Gas and Fuel Associates, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 85)
- Eaton Manufacturing Division, Wilcox-Rich Division, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- The Eclipse Lumber Company, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Eclipsed Moulded Products Company, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ed. Friedrich, Inc., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Gaynor News Company, Inc., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Geigy Company, Inc., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Efco Manufacturing, Inc., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Eichleay Corporation, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Elastic Stop Nut Corporation, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- El Dorado Water Company, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Electric City Dyeing Company, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Electric Vacuum Cleaners Company, International Molders Union of North America (Local 430), 1941 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Electronics Equipment Co, Inc., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Elgin-Joliet and Eastern Railway Company, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Ellis-Klatscher & Co., 1943 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- The Elyria Telephone Company, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Empire Ordinance Company and West Pittston Iron Works, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- R.L. Emery Jr. d/b/a Emery's Motor Coach Lines, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Empire Ordinance Company and West Pittston Iron Works, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Electronics Equipment Co., Inc., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- English Mica Company, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Enid Cooperative Creamery Association, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Entwistle Manufacturing Co., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Building and Construction Trades Council of Pittsburgh, PA, and vicinity, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- I. Spiewak & Sons, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Henry G. Mayer, d/b/a Cherokee Hosiery Mills, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Henry V. Rabouin, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Highland Park Manufacturing Co. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Two cases: one in 1939, the other in 1950
- Henry Trailer Company, a Corporation, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- The Hills Brothers Company, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- H.G. Hill Stores, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- The Hinde and Dauch Paper Company, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- O.U. Hofmann and Sons, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Hollywood-Maxwell Company, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- D.H. Holmes Company, Ltd., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Holtville Ice and Cold Storage Company, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Home Beneficial Life Insurance Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 36)